Testing URL: https://twtb8kdn28.execute-api.eu-central-1.amazonaws.com/quiz

Request 1...
Status: 200
RESULT: FALLBACK DETECTED
{
  "question": "Fallback: During Care Under Fire, what is the only medically indicated intervention?",
  "options": [
    "Airway management",
    "Tourniquet application",
    "Needle decompression",
    "IV access"
  ],
  "correct_index": 1,
  "explanation": "Hemorrhage control via tourniquet is the only approved intervention in CUF."
}

Request 2...
Status: 200
RESULT: SUCCESS (Generated)
{
  "question": "A soldier is shot in the leg and is bleeding profusely. The soldier is in a combat zone and cannot be evacuated immediately. What is the first step in treating the wound?",
  "options": [
    "Apply a tourniquet to the affected limb",
    "Apply a hemostatic agent to the wound",
    "Stop the bleeding by applying pressure with a gauze",
    "Administer a pain medication to the soldier"
  ],
  "correct_index": 0,
  "explanation": "The first step in treating a combat casualty is to control the bleeding. Applying a tourniquet to the affected limb is the most effective way to stop the bleeding in a combat zone where evacuation is not immediately possible."
}

Request 3...
Status: 200
RESULT: FALLBACK DETECTED
{
  "question": "Fallback: During Care Under Fire, what is the only medically indicated intervention?",
  "options": [
    "Airway management",
    "Tourniquet application",
    "Needle decompression",
    "IV access"
  ],
  "correct_index": 1,
  "explanation": "Hemorrhage control via tourniquet is the only approved intervention in CUF."
}
